Guide to the Stanford University, Libraries, Department of Special Collections and University Archives, Records SC0756
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Libraries, Department of Special Collections and University Archives, records
1969-2011
bulk
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University. Libraries. Department of Special Collections and University Archives
SC0756
93.25 Linear Feet
Records include administrative files from the manuscript, rare book, and university archives divisions; exhibit files; and copy negatives for reproductions of items from the collections.
Information about Access
Materials in accession 2017-304 are restricted for 75 years. Otherwise, this collection is open for research.
Acquisition Information
Records were received via administrative transfers, 1990-2011.
Description of the Collection
Records include administrative files from the manuscript, rare book, and university archives divisions; exhibit files; and copy negatives for reproductions of items from the collections.
Academic libraries; Stanford University. Libraries. Department of Special Collections and University Archives; Stanford University. Libraries. Department of Special Collections and University Archives; Stanford University. Libraries. Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Records, Accession ARCH_1993_131
  - AACR 2 (Box 1)
  - Anglo-American Cataloging Rules (AACR II) (Box 1)
  - Academic Planning Office (Box 1)
  - Academic Secretary (Box 1)
  - Acquisitions Department (Box 1)
  - Acquisitions: Gifts, 1976-77 (Box 1)
  - Acquisitions--Purchases--pre1974-75 (Box 1)
  - Acquisitions--Purchases--1974-75 (Box 1)
  - Acquisitions--Purchases, 1976-78 (Box 1)
  - Acquisitions/Purchases 1984-- (Box 1)
  - Adding Machine (Box 1)
  - Addresses (Box 1)
  - Administrative Manual (Box 1)
  - Administrative Services (Box 1)
  - Alumni Association, Correspondence (Box 1)
  - American Institute of Physics: Center for History of Physics (Box 1)
  - American Library Association (Box 1)
  - American Psychological Association (Box 1)
  - Annual Report, 1976-77 (Box 1)
  - Annual Report, 1977-78 (Box 1)
  - Annual Report, 1978-79 (Box 1)
  - Annual Report, 1978-79 (copy) (Box 1)
  - Annual Report 1980-81 (Box 1)
  - Annual Report 1981-82 (Box 1)
  - Annual Statistics (Box 1)
  - Appraisals (Box 1)
  - Appreciation of Service of University Archives (Box 1)
  - Ad: Architectural Records (Box 1)
  - Archival Material not under our "control" (loans, permanent display) (Box 1)
  - Archival Professional Positions (Box 1)
  - Archive of Recorded Sound (Box 1)
  - Archives Administration, Institute for (Box 1)
  - Archives Committee (Box 1)
  - Archives--Establishment of (at Stanford and elsewhere) (Box 1)
  - Archives, Stanford University (Box 1)
  - Staff Meetings - Minutes 1982 (Box 1)
  - Associates of Stanford University Libraries (Box 1)
  - Stanford Associates - Special Projects Comm. (Box 1)
  - Association of American Universities, Correspondence (Box 1)
  - Athletic Department (Box 1)
  - Automation (Box 1)
  - Babbage Institute (Box 1)
  - Bancroft Library, Correspondence (Box 1)
  - Basement "clean-up" (Box 1)
  - Basement Map (Box 2)
  - Basement Sign-out Sheets (Box 2)
  - Basement Sign-out Sheets -- 1979/80 (Box 2)
  - Basement Renovation (Box 2)
  - Basement Problems (Box 2)
  - Basement Stacks (Box 2)
  - Bay Area Archivists (Box 2)
  - Bender Elevator (Box 2)
  - Bender Room (Box 2)
  - Bender Room - Equipment Furniture (Box 2)
  - Bender Room - Move (Box 2)
  - Bender Room (Pre 1979) (Box 2)
  - Bender Room - Other Suggestions (Box 2)
  - Bender Room Opening Celebration (May 10, 1986) (Box 2)
  - Bender Room Opening - Keepsake (Box 2)
  - Bender Room Tea for Library Staff (Box 2)
  - Bender Room, 1986 (Box 2)
  - Bindery - Active (Box 2)
  - Bindery - Inactive (Box 2)
  - Bindery - Policy Procedures (Box 2)
  - Binding and Finishing (Box 2)
  - Black View (Box 2)
  - Book Orders - 1986 (Box 2)
  - Book Orders - 1987 (Box 2)
  - Boise State University (Box 2)
  - Breer, Carl -- Correspondence (Box 2)
  - Brigham Young University (Box 2)
  - Brochure (Box 2)
  - Budget, 1974 - 1979 (Box 2)
  - Budget FY 1978-79, 1979-80 (Box 2)
  - Budget request, 1980-81 (Box 2)
  - Budget request, 1981-1982 (Box 2)
  - Budget FY 1982-83 (Box 2)
  - Budget Planning 82-83 (Box 2)
  - Budget FY 83-84 (Box 2)
  - Budget FY 1983-1984 (Box 2)
  - Budget FY 1984-85 (Box 2)
  - Budget 85-86G (Box 2)
  - Budget FY 87 (Box 2)
  - Budget 1985-86 (Box 2)
  - Budget -- for year 1987 (1986-87) (Box 2)
  - Budget: Nuggets Fund (Box 2)
  - Budget Priorities Commission (Box 2)
  - Budget: Terman Project (Box 2)
  - Budget: U.A. S.C. (general staff) (Box 2)
  - Budget Finance (Box 2)
  - Building Maintenance Equipment (Box 2)
  - Byrne Portraits (Box 2)
  - California Historical Records Educational and Consultant Services (Box 2)
  - Correspondence: California Historical Society (Box 2)
  - California Railroad Museum (Box 2)
  - Cal. St. RR Museum (Box 2)
  - California State Archives (Box 2)
  - California Street Cable Railroad Co. (Box 2)
  - California, University of: University Archivist (Box 2)
  - California, University of: Berkeley (Box 2)
  - Campus Report (Box 2)
  - Canfield Fund (David H. Canfield) (Box 2)
  - Capitol Equipment Requests (Box 2)
  - Card Catalog (Box 2)
  - Carnegie Institute: Dept. of Plant Biology (Box 2)
  - Catalog Department (Box 2)
  - Cataloging (Box 2)
  - Cataloging Advisory Council - Minutes (Box 2)
  - Cataloging Policy Coord. Comm. (Box 2)
  - Cataloging Rules (Box 2)
  - Catalog Filing Rules (Box 2)
  - Catalog of Collections (Box 2)
  - Centennial - A.S.S.U. (Box 2)
  - ASSU Centennial Comm. (Box 2)
  - Centennial Exhibits (Box 2)
  - Centennial -- Miscellaneous (Box 2)
  - Centennial Logo (Box 2)
  - Centennial Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 2)
  - Centennial (Box 2)
  - Centennial, 1991, 1985 (Box 2)
  - Center for Research on Women (Box 3)
  - Center for the History of Chemistry (Box 3)
  - Chadwyck-Healy, Inc. (Box 3)
  - Chaparral (Box 3)
  - Chronology (Stanford Univ.) corrections and additions (Box 3)
  - Circulation 1978-79 (Box 3)
  - Circulation Statistics 1979-1980 (Box 3)
  - Circulation 80-81: 1981 (Winter) (Box 3)
  - Circulation 80-81: 1981 (Spring) (Box 3)
  - Circulation 80-81: 1980 (7/80-12/80) (Fall) (Box 3)
  - Summer Quarter 1981-1982 Circulation Stats (Box 3)
  - Fall Quarter Statistics 1981-1982: Circ. Log and Quarterly Stats (Box 3)
  - Wtr. Qtr. Stats 1/82 - 3/82: Circulation and Quarterly (Box 3)
  - Spring Quarter 1981-1982: Circulation and Quarterly Stats (Box 3)
  - Clark, Birge -- Correspondence (Box 3)
  - Archives, Stanford University: Classification Scheme (4-digit) (Box 3)
  - Cranks (Box 3)
  - Collection Development (Box 3)
  - Collection Development Coordinating Committee (CDCC) (Box 3)
  - Collection Development Council (Box 3)
  - Collection Development Group (Box 3)
  - Collection Dev. Group (Box 3)
  - CDP - Curators Group (Box 3)
  - Curators Group, 1982-83 (Box 3)
  - Collection Development Program -- Directors' Group (Box 3)
  - CDP -- Soc. Sci. Discussion Group (Box 3)
  - Collections - Spurious (Box 3)
  - Correspondence - Colton Case (Box 3)
  - Commission on librarianship (Box 3)
  - Committee for Art (Box 3)
  - Correspondence: Committee Minutes (Box 3)
  - Committee Minutes (Ralph Hansen's file) (Box 3)
  - Computer Science (Box 3)
  - Conservation (Box 3)
  - Conservation Advisory Council (Box 3)
  - Conservation. Advisory Council (Box 3)
  - Conservation Advisory Group (Box 3)
  - Conservation Office (Box 3)
  - Controllers Office (Box 3)
  - Correspondence re: Controller's Office Records 11-68 (Box 3)
  - COPAR (Cooperative Preservation of Architectural Records) (Box 3)
  - Copyright (Box 3)
  - Copyright - Requests tor permission to publish (Box 3)
  - Copyright - Permission to publish (Box 3)
  - Cornell University Archives (Box 3)
  - Cornell University (Box 3)
  - Cowley Project (Box 3)
  - Crothers Papers and Crothers Fund (Manuscript) 1960-67 (Box 3)
  - Custodial Service (Box 3)
  - Dataease: Review (Box 3)
  - Deposits--Records (S.U.A) 9/82 - 11/87 (Box 3)
  - Development Office (Box 3)
  - Director's Meeting (material for D.W.) (Box 3)
  - Directors - PM Meetings (Box 3)
  - Director's Office (Box 3)
  - Disaster guidelines, Priorities (Box 3)
  - Discarded Records (Box 3)
  - Donohoe-Kelly Banking Co. Collection (Box 3)
  - Donor Reports (Box 3)
  - Donor Report 79-80 (Box 3)
  - Donor Report 1978-79 (Box 3)
  - Donor Report 1980-81 (Box 3)
  - Donor Report, 1982 (Box 3)
  - Donor Report 85-86 (Box 3)
  - Correspondence: Dolph, Cyrus (Box 3)
  - Dowler, Lawrence (Box 3)
  - Earthquake Preparedness (Box 4)
  - Earth Sciences History Group (Box 4)
  - Earth Sciences History Group (Box 4)
  - Emergencies (Box 4)
  - Endowed Curatorship (Box 4)
  - Equipment (Box 4)
  - Equipment Repairs (Box 4)
  - Ethics, Professional (Box 4)
  - Evaluations - Students (Box 4)
  - Events -- 1987 (Box 4)
  - Expenses (Box 4)
  - Faculty Papers (Box 4)
  - Felton Vault (Box 4)
  - Fine Printing (Box 4)
  - Foothill Electronics Museum (Box 4)
  - Forms - Other repositories (Box 4)
  - Freshman Orientation (Box 4)
  - Freshman Seminars (Box 4)
  - Fumigation (Insects, Fungus, Bats) (Box 4)
  - Furniture (Box 4)
  - Gay and Lesbian Alliance (Box 4)
  - Gay and Lesbian Records (Box 4)
  - Correspondence: General Secretary's Office (Box 4)
  - Gifts and Exchange (Box 4)
  - Gifts--General--July 1967-June 1968 (Box 4)
  - Gifts--General--July 1968-June 1969 (Box 4)
  - Gifts--General--July 1969-June 1970 (Box 4)
  - Gifts--General--July 1970-June 1971 (Box 4)
  - Gifts--General--July 1971-June 1972 (Box 4)
  - Gifts--General--July 1972-June 1973 (Box 4)
  - Gifts--General--July 1973-June 1974 (Box 4)
  - Gifts--General--July 1974-June 1975 (Box 4)
  - Gifts--General--July 1975-June 1976 (Box 4)
  - Glass Slides and Negatives, Correspondence (Box 4)
  - Glover, Fred -- Correspondence (Box 4)
  - Goals (Box 4)
  - Graduate Studies, Office of: "Directions for preparing Doctoral Dissertations" (Box 4)
  - Grants: MEA Title IIc: MSS Format (Box 4)
  - Title II C -- second year (Box 4)
  - Admin Files: Graphics (of Stanford) (Box 4)
  - Graphics (Box 4)
  - Graphics in West Wing (Box 4)
  - Graphics and Printing Services; Copy Center Account Statements (Box 4)
  - Green Library (Box 4)
  - Guide to the Stanford University Archives (Box 4)
  - Guide - Original (Box 4)
  - Guides - Other Repsoitories (Box 4)
  - Hanna Paul (Box 4)
  - Hansen, Ralph (Box 4)
  - Heating (Box 4)
  - Health Problems -- Renovation (Box 4)
  - Hillel Association: Correspondence (Box 4)
  - Historic Index Committee (Box 4)
  - Historic Points Survey (Box 4)
  - Historic Resources Inventory (Box 4)
  - Historic Values Index: working group (Box 4)
  - History Dept. (Box 4)
  - History of Stanford Course (Box 4)
  - Honors Papers - Political Science: Correspondence (Box 4)
  - Honors Papers (Box 4)
  - Honors Papers - Biological Sciences: Correspondence (Box 4)
  - Honors Papers - Economics: Correspondence (Box 4)
  - Honors Papers - English Dept.: Correspondence (Box 4)
  - Honors Papers - History: Correspondence (Box 4)
  - Honors Papers - Humanities: Correspondence (Box 4)
  - Honors Program - General: Correspondence (Box 4)
  - Hoover Archives (Box 4)
  - Hopkins Marine Station (Box 4)
  - UArch Admin: Hopkins Room (Box 4)
  - Hopkins Room (Box 4)
  - Hopkins Transportation Library (incl. mss collections in S.C.) (Box 4)
  - Humanities and Science, deans office (Box 4)
  - IBM -- PC (Box 4)
  - Personal Computer (hardware, software) (Box 4)
  - Inter-library loan (Box 4)
  - Information Exchange: Correspondence (Box 4)
  - Information Technology Services (Box 4)
  - Intern Program in Archives (Box 4)
  - Internship (Box 4)
  - Inventory (Box 4)
  - Investment Management Organization (Box 4)
  - Invoices, 1976-1977 (Box 4)
  - Invoices, 1977-1978 (Box 4)
  - Invoices, 1978-1979 (Box 4)
  - Invoices, 1979-1980 (Box 4)
  - Invoices, 1980-1981 (Box 4)
  - Invoices, 1981-1982 (Box 4)
  - Invoice form - revision (Box 4)
  - Jackson Library Mss. Collections (Box 4)
  - Keys (Box 4)
  - KQED Auction (Box 4)
  - KTEH -- T.V. (Box 4)
  - Labor Archives (Box 5)
  - Lane Library (Box 5)
  - Larwood Co. (Box 5)
  - Letters to Editors re: misinformation etc. (Box 5)
  - Lewis Clark, Oregon (Box 5)
  - L.S.O (Box 5)
  - L.S.O -- Truck (Box 5)
  - Libraries -- Committee on Committee Use Communications (Box 5)
  - Libraries -- Library Cabinet (Box 5)
  - Libraries -- (S.U.) Resource Guide (Box 5)
  - Libraries -- Staff Orientation (Box 5)
  - Libraries, Visiting Committee % for '75 (Box 5)
  - Library - General (Box 5)
  - Library Archives, 1904-1939 ( Hand Written Register) (Box 5)
  - Library Archives (Box 5)
  - Library Associates (Box 5)
  - Library Cabinet - Meeting Minutes (Box 5)
  - Library Cabinet (Box 5)
  - Library Cabinet - Agenda (Box 5)
  - Curators Group 83-84 (Box 5)
  - Library Development Office (Box 5)
  - Library Goals and Objectives (Box 5)
  - Library Literature Retrieval Service (Box 5)
  - Library Management Development Program (Box 5)
  - Library of Congress - NUCMC (Box 5)
  - Library Staff (Time Survey Forms) (Box 5)
  - Library Survey (Box 5)
  - Loans, Active (Box 5)
  - Loan Statements, 1974-75 -- inactive (Box 5)
  - Loans -- Inactive -- 1975-76 (Box 5)
  - Loans, inactive 1976-77 (Box 5)
  - Loans, inactive 1977-78 (Box 5)
  - Loans, inactive 1978-79 (Box 5)
  - Loans, inactive 1979-80 (Box 5)
  - Loans, inactive 1980-81 (Box 5)
  - Untitled [Loans, inactive 1981-82] (Box 5)
  - Loans/returned 1982-85 (Box 5)
  - Loans, inactive--1985/86 (Box 5)
  - Loans, inactive--1986/87 (Box 5)
  - Loans, Inactive -- 1985- (Box 5)
  - Loans -- Policy (includes "masters" for forms) (Box 5)
  - Loans -- registered locations (Box 5)
  - Lodging -- local (Box 6)
  - LPPS (Box 6)
  - LPPC Task Force #1 (Box 6)
  - MacGregor, Bruce (Box 6)
  - Mail Room (Box 6)
  - Manuscripts Guidelines Comm. (Collection Development) (Box 6)
  - Map Librarians' Group (Box 6)
  - Map Collection (Box 6)
  - Maps - Spires File (Box 6)
  - Forms Masters - Bibliogs etc. (Box 6)
  - Forms -- Masters (Box 6)
  - Mayfield Curtain (Box 6)
  - Medicine, School of -- Archives history (Box 6)
  - Memorabilia (Box 6)
  - Meyer Audio-Visual (Box 6)
  - micrographics (Box 6)
  - Microtext/Newspaper room (Box 6)
  - Microfilming (Box 6)
  - Microfilming Project (Box 6)
  - Microfilming Reader/Printer (Box 7)
  - Microforms (Box 7)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 7)
  - Mahood, James - Mosher Survey (Box 7)
  - Mother's Club (Box 7)
  - Multimate (Box 7)
  - Music Library (Box 7)
  - Museum Loans--1983 (Box 7)
  - Muybridge Collection (Box 7)
  - Muybridge Historical Landmark (Box 7)
  - Nagel, Gunther (Box 7)
  - National Archives and Records Service (Box 7)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH) (Box 7)
  - NEH--Preservation Programs (Box 7)
  - National Historical Publications and Records Commission (Box 7)
  - NHPRC - MARC Conference (Box 7)
  - National Inventory of Documentary Sources in the United States (Box 7)
  - National Union Catalog of MS Collection - NUCMC (Box 7)
  - NUCMC (Box 7)
  - Near West Campus (Box 7)
  - New Quarters (Box 7)
  - News and Publications (Box 7)
  - News Service -- Photography Dept. (Box 7)
  - News and Publications -- Photo Lab (Box 7)
  - Northern Regional Library Facility (Box 7)
  - Northern Regional Library Board - Special Collections and Archives Subcommittee (Box 7)
  - Northwestern University Archives (Box 7)
  - Older Fremont (book) (Box 7)
  - Older, Mrs. Hon C. (Box 7)
  - Online Catalog Task Force, 1982- (Box 7)
  - Orders -- Miscellaneous (Box 7)
  - Other Repositories: Michigan State University (Box 7)
  - Other Repositories (Box 7)
  - Northwestern University Archives (Box 7)
  - N.Y.U. Archives (other repositories) (Box 7)
  - Oregon Historical Society (Box 7)
  - Correspondence: Smithsonian (Box 7)
  - Walt Disney Archives (Box 7)
  - Wells Fargo Archives (Box 7)
  - Overseas Campuses (Box 7)
  - Palo Alto Farm Kiosk (Box 7)
  - Palo Alto Historical Society (Box 7)
  - Paper Shredder (Box 7)
  - Patron Identification forms, samples (Box 7)
  - Peeps, Stephen (Box 7)
  - Periodicals - online formats (Box 7)
  - Personnel (Box 7)
  - Personnel Policy 86-7 (Box 7)
  - SUL Management Development Program (Box 7)
  - Personnel -- Benefits (Box 7)
  - Personnel -- Inquiries re. Openings (Box 7)
  - Personnel -- LS I Search (Box 7)
  - Personnel -- LS II Search (Box 7)
  - Personnel -- OA III Search (Box 7)
  - Office Assistant III (Box 7)
  - Personnel Office--Salaries (Box 7)
  - Personnel -- STAP (Box 7)
  - Personnel, University (Box 7)
  - Petty Cash (Box 7)
  - Photocopy (Box 7)
  - Photocopy Machine (Box 7)
  - Photocopy Machine (Box 7)
  - Photocopy Orders -- Blank forms (Box 8)
  - Photocopy Orders -- 1976-77 (Box 8)
  - Photocopy Orders -- 1977-78 (Box 8)
  - Photocopy Orders -- 1978-79 (Box 8)
  - Photocopy Orders -- 1979-80 (Box 8)
  - Photocopy Orders -- 1980-81 (Box 8)
  - Photocopy Orders -- 1981-82 (Box 8)
  - Photocopy Orders -- 1982-83 (Box 8)
  - Photocopy Orders -- 1983-84 (Box 8)
  - Photocopy Requests -- 1983-84 (Box 8)
  - Photocopy Orders -- 1984-85 (Box 8)
  - Photocopy Orders -- Policy and Regulations (Box 8)
  - Photocopy Orders -- Requests for Copies (Box 8)
  - Photocopy Service -- Copy Center (Box 8)
  - Photocopy Service (Library) (Box 8)
  - Photocopy Service -- Copico (Box 8)
  - Photograph Collection (Box 8)
  - Photograph Collection -- Procedures (Box 8)
  - Photograph Orders (Box 8)
  - Planning Office (Box 8)
  - Plaques (Box 8)
  - Portraits (Box 8)
  - Portraits -- in Bender Room (Box 8)
  - Portraits -- Presidential (Box 8)
  - Post Card Collection -- Correspondence (Box 8)
  - Poster Collection -- Correspondence (Box 8)
  - Preservation (Box 8)
  - Preservation Microfilming (Box 8)
  - Print Collection -- Correspondence (Box 8)
  - Privacy, Protection of -- Library Committee (Box 8)
  - Project South (Box 8)
  - Project SOuth -- Microfiche (Box 8)
  - Projector (Box 8)
  - Publications -- for sale (Box 8)
  - Public Services Council (Box 8)
  - Public Service Group (Box 8)
  - Publications (Box 8)
  - Publications, University -- Correspondence (Box 8)
  - Publications, University -- indexing of (Box 8)
  - Publications -- Spurious (Box 8)
  - Publications using Archives' material (Box 8)
  - Publicity (Box 8)
  - Publicity (Box 8)
  - Publicity, Archives -- Campus Report Issue: Dec. 2, 1970 Mar. 3, 1971 (Box 8)
  - Quad (Box 8)
  - Questionnaires and Surveys (Box 8)
  - Rambo, William (Box 9)
  - Reagan Library Controversy (Box 9)
  - Receipts (Box 9)
  - Record Inventory Report (Box 9)
  - Records Management (Box 9)
  - Records Management (Box 9)
  - Records (Stanford) (Box 9)
  - Records Management Program (Box 9)
  - Reference (Box 9)
  - Reference Books (Box 9)
  - Reference Department -- Reference Job (Box 9)
  - Reference Dept. -- Reference Job (Box 9)
  - Remote Storage (Box 9)
  - Reprographic Services, 1976-77 (Box 9)
  - Reprographic Service, 1977-78 (Box 9)
  - Reprographic Orders, 1978-1979 (Box 9)
  - Reprographic Orders, 1979-1980 (Box 9)
  - Research Libraries Group (Box 9)
  - RLG -- Manuscripts -- 1979-81 (Box 9)
  - RLG -- Manuscripts -- 1982 (Box 9)
  - RLG Manuscripts/Archives Program (1982-1983) (Box 9)
  - RLG Manuscripts Task Force 1983 (Box 9)
  - RLG Task Force 1984 (Box 9)
  - RLG Archivists "Rump-Group" S.A.A. (Box 9)
  - RLG Advisory Group (Box 9)
  - RLG - Advisory Group (Box 9)
  - RLG -- Archives and Special Collections Task Force (Box 9)
  - RLG Task Force (Box 9)
  - RLIN (Box 9)
  - RLIN -- statistics (Box 9)
  - RLIN -- Manuscripts Format (Box 9)
  - RLIN Trouble Report Forms (Box 9)
  - RLIN AMC Report, August 1985: Accessions by Accession Number (2 copies) (Box 9)
  - RLIN AMC Report, August 1985: Main Entry (2 copies) (Box 9)
  - RLIN AMC Report, August 1985: By Record Group Number (2 copies) (Box 9)
  - RLIN AMC -- S.U. Policy (Box 9)
  - Researchers (Free-lance, available for hire) (Box 9)
  - Restrictions, Policy on (Box 9)
  - Retrievals/Returned 1982-1985 (Box 9)
  - Robison Room (Box 9)
  - Room 305, 312 (Box 9)
  - Room 308 (Box 9)
  - Room 308 (Weiss Room) (Box 9)
  - Room 313 E (Box 9)
  - Room 406 (Box 9)
  - Rubber Stamp Lettering Styles (Box 9)
  - Safes (Box 10)
  - Sales -- Duplicates (Box 10)
  - Sales -- Posters (Box 10)
  - Sample Letters (Box 10)
  - SAMSON (Box 10)
  - San Diego Historical Society (Box 10)
  - San Jose Library - Silicon Valley Information Center (Box 10)
  - San Francisco State University Archives (Box 10)
  - Santa Clara County History (Box 10)
  - Santa Clara County Heritage Inventory (Box 10)
  - Santa Clara County Heritage Commission (Box 10)
  - Science Department (Box 10)
  - SCIRE (Box 10)
  - Search Committees (Box 10)
  - Search Comm: Director's Ass't (Box 10)
  - Search Committees -- Librarian for Services and Operations (Box 10)
  - Security (Box 10)
  - Security Microfilm (Box 10)
  - Security Procedures (Box 10)
  - Serials - Claims, 1967-1975 (Box 10)
  - Serials - Claims, 1976-78 (Box 10)
  - Serials - Claims, 1978-79 (Box 10)
  - Serials - Claims, 1979-80 (Box 10)
  - Serials - Claims and Requests - 1980-81 (Box 10)
  - Serials - Claims and Requests - 1981-82 (Box 10)
  - Serials - Claims, 1983-84 (Box 10)
  - Serials - claims for serials records (Box 10)
  - Serials, Department of (Box 10)
  - Serials - New Serials Titles (Box 10)
  - Serials Project 1981-82 (Box 10)
  - Serials Project 1985- (Box 10)
  - Serials - Policies Procedures (Box 10)
  - Serials - Purchase (Box 10)
  - Serials - SULS (Box 10)
  - Intermezzo 75th Anniv. (Box 10)
  - Shainwald Room (Box 10)
  - Signs (Box 10)
  - Signs (Box 10)
  - Silicon Valley Information Center (Box 10)
  - Silicon Valley Project brochure (Box 10)
  - Slide Talk (Box 10)
  - Freshman Orientation (Box 10)
  - Slide Talk (Box 10)
  - Talk (Box 10)
  - Untitled (Box 10)
  - Slide shows (Box 10)
  - Social Sciences Discussion Group (Box 10)
  - Society of American Archivists (SAA) (Box 10)
  - SAA - Description PAG (Box 10)
  - SAA - Conservation PAG (Box 10)
  - SAA - College and University PAG (Box 10)
  - SAA - PAG - College and University Archives Newsletter (Box 10)
  - SAA - Annual Meeting, 1978 (Box 10)
  - SAA - Meeting 1979, Chicago (Box 10)
  - SAA 1980 (Box 10)
  - SAA '81: Local Arrangements (Box 10)
  - SAA '81: Berkeley (Box 10)
  - SAA 1982 (Box 10)
  - SAA 84 - Wash DC (Box 10)
  - SAA Program Committee, 1986 (Box 10)
  - SAA - Automates Records and Techniques Task Force (Box 10)
  - SAA - Exec. (Box 10)
  - SAA Membership List (Box 10)
  - National Information Systems Task Force (NISTF) (Box 10)
  - SAA - NISTF (Box 10)
  - SAA - NISTF - Working Group (Box 10)
  - Society of American Archivists (Box 10)
  - SAA Publications - list (Box 10)
  - SAA -- Publications Ordered (Box 10)
  - Soc. of American Archivists - Science Committee (Box 10)
  - Society of California Archivist (SCA) (Box 11)
  - SCA (Box 11)
  - SCA (Box 11)
  - SCA (Box 11)
  - SCA - Annual Meeting 1975 (Box 11)
  - SCA - Council Minutes (Box 11)
  - SCA - Elections Committee (Box 11)
  - SCA - Fall Workshop 1980 (Box 11)
  - SCA Meeting (Box 11)
  - SCA - Membership Directory (Box 11)
  - SCA - Newsletter (Box 11)
  - Socrates (Box 11)
  - Socrates - Tech Reports fmt (Box 11)
  - Space - SUA stack area, auxiliary, and other rooms (Box 11)
  - Space - West Stack Planning (Box 11)
  - Special Collections Dept. (Box 11)
  - Special Collections Dept. -- Staff Meetings (Box 11)
  - Special Collections - Manuscripts Division (Box 11)
  - Special Projects (Box 11)
  - Sponsored Projects (Box 11)
  - Staff Meetings (Box 11)
  - Staff Meeting Minutes (SUA and SC) 1986-1987 (Box 11)